Keep your finger on the trigger.
In a Valley of Violence is a western, action film directed by Ti West.
The story of a drifter named Paul who arrives in a small town
seeking revenge on the thugs who murdered his friend.
Sisters Mary Anne and Ellen, who run the town's hotel,
help Paul in his quest for vengeance.
Paul, played by Ethan Hawke.
The Marshal, played by John Travolta.
Mary Anne, played by Taissa Farmiga.
Gilly, played by James Ransone.
Ellen, played by Karen Gillan.
Priest, played by Burn Gorman.
In a Valley of Violence is a 2016 American Western
film written and directed by Ti West.
Jason Blum serves as producer through his
production company Blumhouse Productions.
The film stars Ethan Hawke, Taissa Farmiga, James
Ransone, Karen Gillan, and John Travolta.
In a Valley of Violence had its world premiere at South by Southwest on March 12, 2016, and was released
in a limited release and through video on demand on October 21, 2016, by Focus World.
The film was a commercial failure grossing only $61,797, but received critical
praise for the screenplay, direction, and the performances.
The film explores themes of civil war, revenge, murder, killer, dog.